Pulp：柔软潮湿的物体
低级趣味 印刷简陋的书刊
Forget it  It's too risky  I'm through doing that shit
You always say that, the same thing every time
I'm through, never again, too dangerous
I know that's what I always say  I'm always right, too
But you forget about it in a day or two
Well, the days of me forgetting are over and the days of me remembering have just begun
You know when you go on like this what you sound like?
I sound like a sensible fucking man
You sound like a duck  Quack, quack, quack
Take heart, cause you're never gonna have to hear it again since I'm never gonna do it again you're never gonna have to hear me quack about how I'm never gonna do it again
After tonight
Correct  I got all tonight to quack
Can I get anyone more coffee
Oh, yes  Thank you
You're welcome
I mean, the way it is now you're taking the same risk as when you rob a bank
You take more of a risk  Banks are easier
Federal banks ain't supposed to stop you in any way during a robbery
They're insured  Why should they give a fuck?
You don't even need a gun in a federal bank
I heard about this one bloke He walks into a bank with a portable phone  He gives the phone to the teller
bloke on the other end of the phone says
We got this guy's little girl  If you don't give him all your money we're gonna kill her
Did it work
Fucking way, it works  That's what I'm talking about! Knucklehead walks into a bank with a telephone
not a pistol, not a shotgun a fucking phone  Cleans the place out  They don't even lift a fucking finger
Did they hurt the little girl
I don't know  Probably never was a girl in the first place
The point of the story isn't the girl  The point of the story is
they robbed a bank with a telephone
You want to rob banks
I'm not saying I want to rob banks  If we did, it would be easier than what we been doing
No more liquor stores
What we been talking about? Yeah, no more liquor stores
Besides, it ain't the giggle it used to be  There's too many foreigners own liquor stores  Vietnamese, Koreans, they don't even speak fucking English
You tell 'em, Empty out the register  they don't know what the fuck you're talking about
They make it too personal  We keep on, one of these gook fucker's gonna make us kill him
I'm not gonna kill anybody
I don't want to kill anybody, either
But they'll probably put us in a situation where it's us or them
And if it's not the gooks, it's these old fucking Jews
who've owned the store for fifteen fucking generations
who've owned the store for fifteen fucking generations  You got Grandpa Irving sitting behind the counter with a fucking Magnum in his hand
Try walking into one of those places with nothing but a phone
See how far that gets you  Fuck it  We're out of it
Yeah, well, what then? Day jobs
- Not in this life    - What, then
Garcon! Coffee!
This place
Garcon means  boy
This place? A coffee shop
What's wrong with that
Nobody ever robs restaurants  Why not
Bars, liquor stores, gas stations you get your head blown off sticking up one of them
Restaurants, on the other hand, you catch with their pants down
They're not expecting to get robbed  Not as expecting, anyway
I bet you could cut down on the hero factorin a place like this
Same as banks, these places are insured
Manager  he don't give a fuck
He's just trying to get you out the door before you start plugging the diners
Waitresses? Fucking forget it  No way they're taking a bullet for the register
Busboys, some wetback getting paid $1 50 an hour really give a fuck you're stealing from the owner
Customers sitting with food in their mouths  They don't know what's going on  One minute they're having a Denver omelette next minute, someone's sticking a gun in their face
See, I got the idea
last liquor store we stuck up  Remember? All the customers kept coming in
Yeah
You got the idea taking their wallets
- Now, that was a good idea    - Thank you
- Made more from the wallets than we did from the register    - Yes, we did
A lot of people come into restaurants
A lot of wallets
Pretty smart, huh
Pretty smart
I'm ready  Let's do it  Right now, right here  Come on
All right  Same as last time, remember? You're crowd control  I handle employees
I love you, Pumpkin
I love you, Honey Bunny
Everybody, be cool! This is a robbery!
Any of you fucking pricks move and I'll execute every motherfucking last one of you!
低俗小说
主演：约翰·屈夫塔
主演：萨缪尔·杰克逊
主演：乌玛·瑟曼
主演：布鲁斯·威利
OK, so tell me again about the hash bars
OK  What you want to know
Hash is legal there, right
Yeah, it's legal, but it ain't 100% legal  You just can't walk into a restaurant
roll a joint, and start puffing away
I mean, they want you to smoke in your home or certain designated places
And those are hash bars
Yeah, it breaks down like this  It's legal to buy it, it's legal to own it
and if you're the proprietor of a hash bar it's legal to sell it
It's legal to carry it, but    but that doesn't matter cause, get a load of this, all right
If you get stopped by a cop in Amsterdam it's illegal for them to search you
I mean, that's a right the cops in Amsterdam don't have
Oh, man, I'm going  That's all there is to it  I'm fucking going
I know, baby  You'd dig it the most
But you know what the funniest thing about Europe is
- What?   - It's the little differences
I mean, they got the same shit over there that they got here but it's just a little different
Example
You can go to a movie theater in Amsterdam and buy a beer  And I don't mean just, like, in no paper cup
I'm talking about a glass of beer
And in Paris, you can buy a beer at McDonald's
And you know what they call a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese in Paris
They don't call it a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese
No, man, they got the metric system there  They wouldn't know what the fuck a Quarter-Pounder is
What do they call it
They call it a  Royale with Cheese
- Royale with Cheese    - That's right
What do they call a Big Mac
Big Mac's a Big Mac, but they call it Le Big Mac
Le Big Mac
What do they call a Whopper
I don't know  I didn't go into Burger King
You know what they put on French fries in Holland instead of ketchup
- What?    - Mayonnaise
Ha ha ha  I've seen 'em do it, man
They fucking drown 'em in that shit  We should have shotguns for this kind of deal
How many up there
Three or four
That's counting our guy
I'm not sure
So that means it could be up to five guys up there
It's possible
We should have fucking shotguns
What's her name
- Mia    - Mia
How did Marsellus and her meet
I don't know  However people meet people
She used to be an actress
Oh, really? She do anything I'd have seen
I think her biggest deal was she starred in a pilot
Pilot? What's a pilot
Well, you know the shows on TV
I don't watch TV
Yeah, but you are aware that there's an invention called television and on this invention they show shows, right
Yeah
The way they pick TV shows, they make one show  That show's called a pilot
Then they show that one show to the people who pick shows
and on the strength of that one show they decide if they want to make more shows
Some get chosen and become television programs
Some don't, become nothing
She starred in one of the ones that became nothing
You remember Antwan Rockamora?
Half-black, half-Samoan used to call him "Tony Rocky Horror"
Yeah, maybe  Fat, right
I wouldn't go so far as to call the brother fat  I mean, he got a weight problem  What's the nigger gonna do, he's Samoan
Yeah, I think I know who you mean  What about him
Well, Marsellus fucked him up good
Word around the campfire is it was on account of Marsellus Wallace's wife
- So, what'd he do, fuck her?   - No, no, no, no, no  Nothing that bad
Well, then, what, then
Gave her a foot massage
A foot massage
That's it
Then what did Marsellus do
Sent a couple of cats over to his place
They took him out on his patio, threw his ass over the balcony  Nigger fell four stories  They had a little garden down at the bottom enclosed in glass, like a greenhouse
Nigger fell through that
Since then, he kind of developed a speech impediment
That's a damn shame
But still, I have to say you play with matches, you get burned
What do you mean
You don't be giving Marsellus Wallace's new bride a foot massage
You don't think he overreacted
Well, Antwan probably didn't expect Marsellus to react the way he did, but he had to expect a reaction  It was a foot massage  A foot massage is nothing
I give my mother a foot massage
No, it's laying hands in a familiar way on Marsellus' new wife  I mean, is it as bad as eating her pussy out? No, but it's the same fucking ballpark
Whoa, whoa, whoa, stop right there
Eating a bitch out and giving a bitch a foot massage ain't even the same fucking thing
It's not  It's the same ballpark
Ain't no fucking ballpark, neither
Now, look, maybe your method of massage differs from mine
but you know touching his wife's feet and sticking your tongue in her holiest of holies ain't the same fucking ballpark  It ain't the same league  It ain't even the same fucking sport
Look, foot massages don't mean shit
Have you ever given a foot massage
Don't be telling me about foot massages  I'm the foot fucking master
You given a lot of 'em
Shit, yeah  Got my technique down and everything  I don't be tickling or nothing
Would you give a guy a foot massage
Fuck you
- You given 'em a lot?   - Fuck you
You know, I'm kind of tired  I could use a foot massage myself
Yo, yo, yo, man  You best back off  I'm getting a little pissed here
- This is the door    - There it is
What time you got
7:22 in the a.m
No, it ain't quite time yet  Come on  Let's hang back
Just 'cause I wouldn't give no man a foot massage don't make it right for Marsellus
to throw Antwan off a building into a glass motherfucking house fucking up the way the nigger talks  That shit ain't right
Motherfucker do that shit to me, he better paralyze my ass cause I'd kill the motherfucker you know what I'm saying
I ain't saying it's right
But you're saying a foot massage don't mean nothing and I'm saying it does
I've given a million ladies a million foot massages and they all meant something
Now, we act like they don't, but they do  That's what's so fucking cool about 'em
There's a sensuous thing going on where, you know you don't talk about it
but you know it, and she knows it
Fucking Marsellus knew it and Antwan should've fucking better known better
I mean, that's his fucking wife, man  This ain't a man with a sense of humor about this shit
You know what I'm saying
It's an interesting point  Come on  Let's get into character
What's her name again
- Mia    - Mia
Why you so interested in big man's wife
Well, he's going out of town, Florida and he asked me if I'd take care of her while he's gone
- Take care of her?   - No, man  Just take her out
You know, show her a good time  Make sure she don't get lonely
You're gonna be taking Mia Wallace out on a date
It is not a date
It's just like if you were going to take your buddy's wife to a movie or something
It's just good company, that's all
It's not a date  It's definitely not a date
Hey, kids  How you boys doing
Hey, keep chilling
You know who we are
We're associates of your business partner Marsellus Wallace
You do remember your business partner, don't you
Let me take a wild guess here
You're Brett, right
Yeah  I thought so
You remember your business partner Marsellus Wallace don't you, Brett
Yeah, I remember him
Good  Looks like me and Vincent caught you boys at breakfast
Sorry about that  What you having
- Hamburgers    - Hamburgers!
The cornerstone of any nutritious breakfast
What kind of hamburgers
Ch-ch-cheeseburgers
No, no, no, no  Where'd you get 'em? McDonald's, Wendy's, Jack-in-the-Box, where?
Um, Big Kahuna Burger
Big Kahuna Burger  That's that Hawaiian burger joint
I hear they got some tasty burgers  I ain't never had one myself  How are they
- They're good    - You mind if I try one of yours
- This is yours here, right?  - Yeah
Mmm! This is a tasty burger
Vincent, you ever had a Big Kahuna Burger
Want a bite? They're real tasty
I ain't hungry
If you like burgers, give 'em a try sometime
Me, I can't usually get 'em 'cause my girlfriend's a vegetarian which pretty much makes me a vegetarian
But I do love the taste of a good burger
You know what they call a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese in France
- No    - Tell him, Vincent
Royale with Cheese
You know why they call it that
Because of the metric system
Check out the big brain on Brett!
You're a smart motherfucker  That's right  The metric system
What's in this
- Sprite  - Sprite, good
You mind if I have some of your tasty beverage to wash this down with
Go right ahead
That hit the spot
You, Flock of Seagulls  You know why we're here
Why don't you tell my man Vince here where you got the shit hid at
- It's over there    - I don't remember asking you a goddamn thing!
You were saying
It's in the cupboard
N-no  The one by your kn-knees
Vincent
We happy
Yeah, we happy  Pbbbt
Look  I'm sorry, uh, I didn't get your name
- I got yours  Uh, Vincent, right?   - But I never got yours
My name's Pitt and your ass ain't talking your way out of this shit
I just want you to know how
I just want you to know how sorry we are that things got so fucked up with us and and Mr.Wallace
W-we got into this thing with the best intentions  I never
Oh, I'm sorry  Did I break your concentration
I didn't mean to do that  Please, continue
You were saying something about  best intentions
What's the matter? Oh, y-you were finished
Oh, well, allow me to retort
What does Marsellus Wallace look like
What
What country are you from
Wh-what
Why no country I ever heard of, they speak English in What?
- English, motherfucker! Do you speak it?   - Yes!
Then you know what I'm saying
Describe what Marsellus Wallace looks like!
What? I
Say "what" again! Say "what" again!
I dare you! I double-dare you, motherfucker! Say "what" one more goddamn time!
- H-h-he's black   - Go on!
He's bald
Does he look like a bitch
What
No!
Then why you try to fuck him like a bitch, Brett?  - I didn't
Yes, you did  Yes, you did, Brett! You tried to fuck him
Marsellus Wallace don't like to be fucked by anybody except Mrs  Wallace
You read the Bible, Brett
Y-yes
Well, there's this passage I got memorized
sort of fits this occasion  Ezekiel 25:17
The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the selfish and the tyranny of evil men
Blessed is he who in the name of charity and good will
shepherds the weak through the Valley of Darkness
for he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children
And I will strike down upon thee "with great vengeance and furious anger those who attempt to poison and destroy My brothers
And you will know My name is the Lord when I lay My vengeance upon thee!
(魏文生与马沙之妻)
I think you're gonna find
when all this shit is over and done
I think you're gonna find yourself one smiling motherfucker
Thing is, Butch,
right now you got ability
But painful as it may be
ability don't last
And your days are just about over
Now, that's a hard motherfucking fact of life but that's a fact of life
your ass is gonna have to get realistic about
See, this business is filled to the brim with unrealistic motherfuckers
motherfuckers who thought their ass would age like wine
If you mean it turns to vinegar, it does
If you mean it gets better with age, it don't
Besides, Butch
how many fights you think you got in you, anyway
Hmm? Two
Boxers don't have an Old-timer's Day
You came close, but you never made it
And if you were gonna make it You would have made it before now
You my nigger
It certainly appears so
Night of the fight, you may feel a slight sting
That's pride fucking with you
Fuck pride!
Pride only hurts  It never helps
You fight through that shit
Cause a year from now when you're kicking it in the Caribbean
you're gonna say to yourself, Marsellus Wallace was right
I got no problem with that, Mr. Wallace
In the fifth, your ass goes down
Say it
In the fifth, my ass goes down
Yo, Vincent Vega, our man in Amsterdam  Jules Winnfield, our man in Inglewood  Get your asses on in here!
Goddamn, nigger! What's up with them clothes
You don't even want to know
Where's the big man
Big man's right over there taking care of some business
Why don't you hang back for a second or two, you know
You see the white boy leave, just go on over
How you been
I've been doing pretty good  How 'bout yourself
All right
So, I hear you're taking Mia out tomorrow
At Marsellus' request
- Have you met Mia?   - Not yet
What's so fucking funny
- Not a goddamn thing    - I got to piss
Look, I'm not a fucking idiot, all right
It's the big man's wife  I'm gonna sit across from her chew my food with my mouth closed laugh at her fucking jokes, and that's it
Hey, my name's Paul, and this shit's between y'all
Then what did you fucking ask me about it for
Asshole
- Filters?   - Nah
You looking at something, friend
You ain't my friend, palooka
What was that
I think you heard me just fine, punchy
Vincent Vega's in the house? My nigger  Get your ass over here
Pack of Red Apples  $ 1 40
And some matches
It's as if it turns every part of your body into the tip of a penis
I'll lend it to you  It's a great book on piercing
Well, you see how they use that gun to pierce your ears? They don't use that to pierce your nipples, too, do they
Forget that gun  That gun goes against the entire idea behind piercing
All my piercing, eighteen places on my body every one of 'em done with a needle
Five in each ear  One through the nipple of my left breast
Two in my right nostril  One in my left eyebrow
One in my belly  One in my lip  One in my clit  And I wear a stud in my tongue
Excuse me
I was just curious, but, um
why would you wear a stud in your tongue
It's a sex thing  Helps fellatio
Vincenzo  Step into my office
This is Panda, from Mexico  Very good stuff
Now, that's Bava  Different, but equally good
And that is Choco, from the Hartz Mountains of Germany
Now, the first two are the same 300 a gram  Those are friend prices
But this one is a little more expensive  This is 500 a gram
but when you shoot it you will know where that extra money went
Now, there's nothing wrong with these two  This is real, real, real good shit
But this one is a fucking madman
Remember, I just got back from Amsterdam
Are we in Inglewood? No  You're in my home
Now, white people who know the difference between good shit and bad shit, this is the house they come to
Now, my shit, I'll take the Pepsi Challenge with that Amsterdam shit any old day of the fucking week
That's a bold statement
This ain't Amsterdam, Vince  This is a seller's market
Coke is fucking dead as dead
Heroin is coming back in a big fucking way
All right, give me three grams of madman
If it's as good as you say it is I'll come back and buy another thousand
Well, I just hope that I still have some left for you
But I'm giving you some out of my own private stash
Hey, I'm out of balloons  Is a baggie all right
Yeah, that's cool
All right  I'll just get one for you
Honey, will you get me some baggies and, uh, twistix from the kitchen
Hey, uh, what do you think about Trudi? She ain't got a boyfriend  You want to, uh, hang out, get high
Which one is Trudi? The one with all the shit in her face
No, that's Jody  That's my wife
I'm sorry, man  Thank you
No, I can't  Um, I gotta be someplace
All right  No problemo
I'll take a rain check
Thank you, Jody
Still got your Malibu
Ah, man  You know what some fucker did the other day
What
Fucking keyed it
Oh, man, that's fucked up
Tell me about it  I had it in storage for 3 years
It was out 5 days and some dickless piece of shit fucked with it
They should be fucking killed, man
No trial, no jury, straight to execution
Boy, I wish I could've caught him doing it
I'd have given anything to catch that asshole doing it
It'a been worth him doing it just so I could've caught him doing it
What a fucker!
What's more chicken shit than fucking with a man's automobile
It's just against the rules
Thank you
Thank you  Mind if I shoot up here
Mi casa, su casa
Muchas gracias
文生 我在换衣服 门没锁
进来弄杯酒喝 蜜儿
Hello
Vincent
I'm on the intercom
Where is it? Where is the intercom
It's on the wall by the two African fellows
To your right
Warm  Warmer  Disco
Hello
Push the button if you want to talk
Go make yourself a drink and I'll be down in two shakes of a lamb's tail
The bar is by the fireplace
OK
Let's go
What the fuck is this place
This is Jack Rabbit Slim's  An Elvis man should love it
Come on, Mia, let's go get a steak
You can get a steak here, daddy-o
Oh, after you, kitty cat
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen  Now, how may I help you
There's a reservation under Wallace
Wallace
We reserved a car
Oh, a car  Why don't you seat them in the Chrysler
Let's hear it for Ricky Nelson! Fantastic job, Rick  Thank you very much
Vincent!
Just so that you all know Ricky will be back in the second half of our show
So we hope you enjoy your meals here at Jack Rabbit Slim's
Phillip    Morris!
What do you think
I think it's like a wax museum with a pulse
Hi, I'm Buddy  What can I get you
Let's see  Steak, steak, steak
Yeah, the Douglas Sirk steak  I'll have that
How do you want that cooked? Burnt to a crisp, or bloody as hell
Bloody as hell, and oh, yeah, look at this  Vanilla Coke
What about you, Peggy Sue
I'll have the Durwood Kirby burger
bloody
and
the $5 00 shake
How do you want that shake? Martin and Lewis, or Amos and Andy
Martin and Lewis
Did you just order a $5 00 shake
Mm-hmm
That's a shake  That's milk and ice cream
Last I heard
That's $5 00
You don't put bourbon in it or nothin
No
Just checkin
I'll be right back with your drinks
Could you, um roll me one of those, cowboy
You can have this one, cowgirl
Thanks
Think nothing of it
So Marsellus said you just got back from Amsterdam
Sure did  How long were you there
Just over three years
I go there about once a year to chill out for a month
No kidding? I didn't know that
Why would you
I heard you did a pilot
That was my fifteen minutes
What was it
It was a show about a team of female secret agents called  Fox Force Five
- What?     - Fox Force Five
Fox, as in we're a bunch of foxy chicks
Force, as in we're a force to be reckoned with
And Five, as in there's one, two, three, four, five of us
There was a blond one    Sommerset O'Neal  She was the leader
The Japanese Fox was a kung-fu master
The black girl was a demolition expert
French Fox's speciality was sex
What was your specialty
Knives
Character I played, Raven McCoy her background was she grew up raised by circus performers
she was the deadliest woman in the world with a knife
and she knew a zillion old jokes
Her grandfather, an old vaudevillian, taught her
And if we would've got picked up they would've worked in a gimmick where every show I would've told another joke
You know any of them old jokes
Well, I only got the chance to say one  cause we only did one show
- Tell me   - It's corny
Don't be that way  Tell me
No  You wouldn't like it, and I'd be embarrassed
You'd be em You told 50 million people, and you can't tell me
I promise I won't laugh
That's what I'm afraid of, Vince
That's not what I meant, and you know it
Well, now I'm definitely not gonna tell you cause it's been built up too much
What a gyp
Martin and Lewis
Vanilla Coke
Mmm Yummy You think I could have a sip of that
Be my guest
I gotta know what a $5 00 shake tastes like
You can use my straw  I don't have cooties
Yeah, but maybe I do
Cooties, I can handle
All right
Goddamn, that's a pretty fucking good milk shake
Told you
I don't know if it was worth $5 00 but it was pretty fucking good
Don't you hate that
Hate what
Uncomfortable silences
Why do we feel it's necessary to yak about bullshit in order to be comfortable
I don't know, but it's a good question
That's when you know you've found somebody really special
when you can just shut the fuck up for a minute and comfortably share a silence
Well, I don't think we're quite there yet but don't feel bad  We just met each other
I'll tell you what
I'm going to go to the bathroom and powder my nose
You sit here and think of something to say
I'll do that
OK
I said goddamn! Goddamn
Mmm  Don't you just love it when you come back from the bathroom to find your food waiting for you? We're lucky we got anything at all
I don't think Buddy Holly's much of a waiter
Maybe we should've sat in Marilyn Monroe's section
Which one? There's two Monroes
No, there's not
That is Marilyn Monroe
And I don't see Jayne Mansfield  She must have the night off or something
Pretty smart
Yeah, I got my moments
So, did you think of something to say
Actually, I did
However
You seem like a really nice person and I don't want to offend you
Ooh  This doesn't sound like the usual mindless, boring getting-to-know-you chitchat
That sounds like you actually have something to say
Well, well, I do  I do
But you have to promise not to be offended
No! No, no, no
You can't promise something like that
I have no idea what you're gonna ask me
and my natural response could be to get offended
I would've broken my promise
Let's just forget it
That's an impossibility, Trying to forget anything as intriguing as this would be an exercise in futility
Is that a fact
Besides, isn't it more exciting when you don't have permission?
All right  All right  Well, here it goes
What did you, uh, think about what happened to Antwan
- Who's Antwan?   - Tony Rocky Horror  You know him
He fell out of a window
Mmm  Mmm  Well, that is one way to say it  Another way to say it would be that he was thrown out
Another way would be was he was thrown out by Marsellus
and yet even another way is to say he was thrown of a window by Marsellus because of you
Is that a fact
No, no  It's not a fact  It's just what I heard
Who told you
They
They talk a lot, don't they
They certainly do  They certainly do
Don't be shy, Vincent  What else did they say
Well, I'm not  I'm not shy  Um
Did it involve the F word
No  No, no, no
They just said that Antwan had given you a foot massage
And
- And nothin   - That's it
You heard Marsellus threw Tony Rocky Horror out of a four-story window for giving me a foot massage
- Mm-hmm  - And you believe that
Well, I mean at the time I was told, it sounded reasonable
Marsellus throwing Tony out of a four-story window for massaging my feet seemed reasonable
No, it seemed excessive but that doesn't mean it didn't happen  I mean, I understand
that Marsellus is very, very protective of you
A husband being protective of his wife is one thing
A husband almost killing another man for touching his wife's feet is something else
But did it happen
Only thing Antwan ever touched of mine was my hand when he shook it at my wedding
Really
Truth is, nobody knows why Marsellus threw Tony out of that four-story window except Marsellus and Tony
But when you little scamps get together you're worse than a sewing circle
Ladies and gentlemen
now the moment you've all been waiting for
the world-famous Jack Rabbit Slim's Twist Contest
This is where one lucky couple will win this handsome trophy that Marilyn here is holding
Now, who'll be our first contestants
Right here!
I wanna dance
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no
I do believe Marsellus    my husband, your boss
told you to take me out and do whatever I wanted
Now I want to dance  I want to win  I want that trophy, so dance good
All right  You asked for it
Let's hear it for our first contestants
Let's meet our first contestants here this evening  Young lady, what is your name
Mrs. Mia Wallace
And how about your fella here
Vincent Vega
All right  Let's see what you can do  Take it away!
Is that what you call an uncomfortable silence
I don't know what you call that
Drinks  Music
I'm gonna take a piss
That's a little bit more information than I needed, Vince, but go right ahead
One drink and that's it
Don't be rude  Drink your drink  But do it quickly
Say good night and go home
You see, this is a moral test of oneself  Whether or not you can maintain loyalty
Because being loyal is very important
So, you're gonna go out there, you're gonna say Good night  I've had a very lovely evening
Walk out the door and get in the car
Go home, jerk off, and that's all you're gonna do
All right, Mia  So, listen, I gotta go  All right
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ
Oh, fuck me! Fuck me!
Oh, come on, girl  We're getting out of here  We gotta walk now
Don't fucking die on me, Mia  Silly fuck
Answer!
Fuck you, Lance! Answer!
Lance! The goddamn phone's ringing!
I can hear it
I thought you told those fucking assholes never to call here this late
Yeah, I told 'em and that is exactly what I'm going to tell this fucking asshole right now
Lance, Vincent  I'm in big fucking trouble, man  I'm coming to your house
Whoa, whoa  Hold your horses, man  Wh-what's the problem
I got this chick, she's fucking O D  Ing on me
Don't bring her here  I'm not even fucking joking with you, man
Don't not be bringing some fucked-up pooh-butt to my house
No choice
She's O D  In
She's fucking dying on me, man!
OK, well, then you bite the fucking bullet and you take her to a hospital and call a lawyer
Negative
This is not my fucking problem, man! You fucked her up, you fucking deal with this!
Are you talking to me on a cellular phone
I don't know you  Who is this? Don't come here  I'm hanging up the phone  Prank caller! Prank caller!
What the hell was that!
Have you lost your fucking mind
You were talking about drug shit on a cellular ph Lance, help me
You crashed your car into my fucking house!
Hey, hey, hey! Are you deaf? You are not bringing this fucked-up bitch into my house!
This fucked-up bitch is Marsellus Wallace's wife  Do you know who Marsellus Wallace is
- Yeah   - If she croaks on me, I'm a fucking grease spot!
I will be forced to tell him that you did not help
and that you let her die on your fucking lawn  Now, come on, help me  Help me  Pick her up
Shit!
Lance!
It's 1:30 in the goddamn morning  What the fuck's going on out here
Who's she
Go to the fridge and get the adrenaline shot
What's wrong with her
She's O D  Ing! Get her out of here!
Get the shot!
Fuck you! Fuck you, too!
What a fucking bitch
Just keep talking to her  She's getting the shot  I'm gonna go get my little black medical book
What the fuck you need a medical book for
I never had to give an adrenaline shot before
You've never given an adrenaline shot
I never had to  I don't go joypopping with a bunch of bubblegummers  My friends can handle their highs
Get the shot!
I am if you'll let me
I ain't fucking stopping you! Well, stop talking to me  Start talking to her!
- Get the shot!   - All right!
Hurry up, Lance! We're losing her!
I'm looking as fast as I can!
What's he looking for
I don't know  Some book
What are you looking for
My little black medical book!
A little black fucking medical book! It's like a textbook they give to nurses
I never saw no medical book  Well, trust me, I have one
If it's so important, why don't you keep it with the shot
I don't know! Stop bothering me!
While you're looking for it, she's gonna die on our carpet  You're never gonna find anything in this mess
Honey, I'm going to fucking kill you if you don't shut up! Get in here!
Get the fuck out of my way
Pig
Quit fucking around and give her the shot
While I'm doing this you take off her shirt and find her heart
It's got to be exact
Yeah, exact  A shot in the heart, so I guess it's gotta be exact
I don't know exactly where her heart is  I think it's here
That's it  This it? What I need is a big fat magic marker
- You got it?   - What
A magic marker! A felt pen! A fucking black magic marker!
All right  Hurry up
Fuck  OK, OK, OK  I think it's ready
Hurry up, man  Hurry up
I'll tell you what to do
No, no, no  You're gonna give her the shot
You're gonna give her the shot  I ain't giving her the shot
I ain't giving her the shot  I never done this before
I ain't never done it before, either  I ain't starting now
You brought her here, that means you're gonna give her the shot
The day I bring an O D  Ing bitch to your house then I give her the shot  Give her the shot
Give it to me  Here  Give me that
Tell me what to do
OK  You're giving her an injection of adrenaline straight to her heart, but she's got a breastplate
You've got to pierce through that
You gotta bring the needle down in a stabbing motion
I gotta stab her three times
No! You don't gotta stab her three times  Just once
But hard enough to get through her breastplate into her heart
Once you do that, you press down on the plunger
OK, then what happens
I'm kind of curious about that myself
This ain't no fucking joke, man! Am I gonna kill her
She's supposed to come out of it like that
All right  Count to three
Ready? One
two
Three!
If you're all right, then say something
Something
Ha ha  That was fucking trippy  Ha ha ha ha
Mia  Mia
what's your thoughts on on on how to handle this
What's yours
Well, I'm of the opinion that if Marsellus lived his whole life he don't need to know nothing about this incident
If Marsellus knew about this incident I'd be in as much trouble as you
I seriously doubt that
I can keep a secret if you can
Shake on it
Mum's the word
Now, if you'll excuse me I'm gonna go home and have a heart attack
Vincent! Do you want to hear my Fox Force Five joke
Sure  Except that I think I'm still a little too petrified to laugh
No, you won't laugh 'cause it's not funny  But if you still wanna hear it, I'll tell it  I can't wait
OK
Three tomatoes are walking down the street Papa Tomato, Mama Tomato, and Baby Tomato
Baby Tomato starts lagging behind and Papa Tomato gets really angry
and Papa Tomato gets really angry goes back and squishes him, and says, Catch up
Ketchup
See you around
Oh, that Paddlefoot    he funny, silly dog  He think totem pole alive  Hee hee hee!
He arctic tenderfoot
That totem pole been here forever
Butch
Butch, stop watching TV a second
- Yeah?   - We got a special visitor
Now do you remember when I told you your daddy died in a P O W  Camp
Well  this here is Captain Koons  He was in the P O W  Camp with Daddy
Hello, little man  Boy, I sure heard a bunch about you
See, I was a good friend of your dad's
We were in that Hanoi pit of hell together over five years
Hopefully you'll never have to experience this yourself
but when two men are in a situation like me and your dad were for as long as we were
you take on certain responsibilities of the other
If it had been me who'd not made it
Major Coolidge would be talking right now to my son Jim
But the way it turned out I'm talking to you
Butch
I got something for you
This watch I got here was first purchased by your great-grandfather during the First World War
It was bought in a little general store in Knoxville, Tennessee
Made by the first company to ever make wristwatches
Up till then, people just carried pocket watches
It was bought by Private Doughboy Erine Coolidge on the day he set sail for Paris
This was your great- grandfather's war watch and he wore it every day he was in that war
And when he'd done his duty he went home to your great-grandmother took the watch off
put it in an old coffee can and in that can it stayed Till your gr anddad, Dane Coolidge
was called upon by his country to go overseas and fight the Germans once again
This time they called it World War II
Your great-grandfather gave this watch to your granddad for good luck
Unfortunately, Dane's luck wasn't as good as his old man's Dane was a marine, and he was killed along with all the other marines at the Battle of Wake Island
Your granddad was facing death  He knew it
None of those boys had any illusions about ever leaving that island alive
so, three days before the Japanese took the island your granddad asked a gunner on an Air Force transport
name of Winocki a man he had never met before in his life
to deliver to his infant son who he had never seen in the flesh his gold watch
Three days later, your granddad was dead but Winocki kept his word
After the war was over he paid a visit to your gr andmother
delivering to your infant father his dad's gold watch
This watch
This watch was on your daddy's wrist when he was shot down over Hanoi
He was captured, put in a Vietnamese prison camp
He knew that if the gooks ever saw the watch they'd confiscate it take it away
The way your dad looked at it, this watch was your birthright
He'd be damned if any slopes put their greasy yellow hands on his boy's birthright, so he hid it
in one place he knew he could hide something his ass
Five long years he wore this watch up his ass
Then he died of dysentery, he give me the watch
I hid this uncomfortable hunk of metal up my ass, two years
Then after seven years I was sent home to my family  And
now
little man, I give the watch to you
It's time, Butch
(金表)
It's official  It's official  Wilson is dead!
Dan, that had to be the bloodiest and the most brutal fight this city has ever seen
Coolidge left faster than I've ever seen a victorious boxer leave the ring
Do you think he knew Wilson was dead
My guess would be yes, Richard  I could see the frenzy in his eyes
give way to the realization of what he was doing  I think any man would have left the ring that fast
Do you feel this tragedy is gonna have an effect on the world of boxing
Such a tragedy can't help but shake the boxing world to its very foundations
but par amount importance is during the sad weeks ahead the eyes of the WBA remain
Marsellus
I didn't do it, man
How you doing
Great  I never thanked you for dinner
- What you got?   - He booked
His trainer
Says he don't know nothing  I believe him
Think Butch surprised his ass same as us
No, we don't wanna think, we wanna know  Take him to the kennel, sic the dogs on his ass
We'll find out for goddamn sure what he knows and what he don't
Butch's search    how do you want it done
I'm prepared to scour the earth for that motherfucker
If Butch goes to Indochina I want a nigger hiding in a bowl of rice ready to pop a cap in his ass
I will take care of it
- Hey, mister?  - What
You were in that fight  The fight on the radio
You're the fighter
Now, what gave you that idea
You're him  I know you're him
Tell me you're him
I'm him
You killed the other boxing man
He's dead
The radio said he was dead
Sorry about that, Floyd
What does it feel like
What does what feel like
Killing a man
Beating another man to death with your bare hands
Are you a weirdo
No  It is a subject I have much interest in
You are the first person I've met who has killed somebody
So what does it feel like to kill a man
I'll tell you what
You give me one of them cigarettes you got up there and I'll tell you all about it
So Esmarelda Villalobos  Is that Mexican
The name is Spanish, but I am Colombian
That's some handle you got there, honey
Thank you  And what is your name
Butch
Butch  What does it mean
I'm an American, honey  Our names don't mean shit
So, moving right along, Esmarelda  What is it you wanna know
I want to know what it feels like to kill a man
I couldn't tell ya
I didn't know he was dead until you told me he was dead
Now that I know he's dead you wanna know how I feel about it
I don't feel the least bit bad about it
What the fuck I tell ya, huh? As soon as the word got out the fix was in, man the odds went through the roof
I know  I know  Unbelievable
If he was a better boxer, he'd still be alive
He never laced up his gloves which he never shoulda done in the first fucking place he'd still be alive
who gives a fuck? It's over now
Well, enough about the poor unfortunate Mr.Floyd  Let's talk about the rich and prosperous Mr.Butch
How many bookies you lay it around on
All eight? How long to collect
So you'll have it all by tomorrow night? No, I understand, a few stragglers aside
No, I understand, a few stragglers aside  Oh, fuck, Scotty, that is good news that is great news, man
No, me and Fabienne are gonna leave in the morning
It'll probably take us a couple of days to get to Knoxville
OK, my brother  You're right  You're goddamn right
All right, Scotty  Next time I see you, we'll be on Tennessee time  Be cool, brother
45 60
And, uh, here's a little    something for the effort
Now if anybody asks you who your fare was tonight what are you gonna say
The truth
Three well-dressed, slightly toasted Mexicans
Bonsoir, Esmarelda Villalobos
Buenas noches, Butch
Keep the light off
Is that better, sugar pop
Oui
Hard day at the office
Pretty hard  I got in a fight
Poor baby  Can we make spoons
You know what? I was thinking about taking a shower  I'm stinking like a dog over here
Mmm  I like the way you stink
Let me take this jacket off
- I was looking at myself in the mirror
I wish I had a pot
You were looking at yourself in the mirror and you wish you had some pot
A pot belly
Pot bellies are sexy
Well, you should be happy cause you have one
Shut up, fatso! I don't have a pot
I have a bit of a tummy like Madonna when she did Lucky Star  It's not the same thing
I didn't know there was such a difference between a pot belly and a tummy
The difference is huge
Would you like it if I had a pot belly
No  Pot bellies make a man Iook either oafish or like a gorilla
But on a woman, a pot belly is very sexy
The rest of you is normal face, normal legs, normal hips,
normal ass but with a big perfectly round pot belly
If I had one, I'd wear a T-shirt two sizes too small to accentuate it
You think men would find that attractive
I don't give a damn what men find attractive
It's unfortunate what we find pleasing to the touch and pleasing to the eye is seldom the same
If you had a pot belly I would punch you in it
You'd punch me in my belly?
Right in the belly
Ah! I'd smother you  I'd drop it right on your face till you couldn't breathe
- You'd do that?   - Yes Yes
- Did you get everything?    - Yes, I did
Good job, sugar pop
Did everything go as planned
You didn't listen to the radio
I never listen to your fights  Were you the winner
I won, all right
Are you still retiring
Sure am
So, it all worked out in the finish
We're not at the finish yet, baby
We're in a lot of danger, aren't we
If they find us, they'll kill us, won't they
But they won't find us, will they
Do you still want me to go with you
I don't want to be a burden or a nuisance, it's
Say it
I want you to be with me
Forever
Forever and ever
Do you love me
Very, very much
- Butch?  - Yes
Will you give me oral pleasure
Will you kiss it
But you first
OK
Butch  Mon amour  L'aventure commence
I think I cracked a rib
Giving me oral pleasure
No, retard  From the fight
Don't call me retard
My name is Fabby  My name is Fabienne
Stop it  Stop it
Shut up, fuckhead! I hate that mongoloid voice
I hate that mongoloid voice
I take it back
Would you hand me a dry towel, Miss Beautiful Tulip
Oh, I like that  I like being called a tulip
Tulip is much better than mongoloid
I didn't call you a mongoloid
I called you a retard, and I took it back
Butch
Yes, lemon pie
Where are we going to go
Well, I'm not sure yet  Wherever you want
We're gonna get a lot of money from this
but it ain't gonna be the kinda money that we can live like hogs in the fat house forever
I was thinking maybe we could go down someplace in the South Pacific
The kinda money we're gonna have is gonna carry us a long way down there
If we wanted, we could live in Bora Bora
You betcha
And if after a while you didn't dig that go someplace else, maybe Tahiti  Mexico
But I do not speak Spanish
Well, you do not speak Bora Boran, either  Besides, Mexican is easy
Donde esta el zapateria
What does that mean
Where is the shoe store
Spit, please
Donde esta el zapateria
Excellent pronunciation
You'll be my little mamacita in no time
Que hor a es
What time is it
Time for bed
Sweet dreams, jellybean
Butch
Never mind
Merde  You startled me  Did you have a bad dream
What is this you're watching
A motorcycle movie  I'm not sure the name
Are you watching it
In a way
It's a little early in the morning for explosions and war
What was it about
How should I know, Fabienne? You were the one who was watching it
No, imbecile, what was your dream about
I don't know  I don't remember
It's really rare that I remember my dreams
Well, let's look at the grumpy man in the morning
Why don't you get up and we'll get some breakfast
One more kiss, and I'll get up
Satisfied
Yep
Then get up, lazy bones
God  Unh  What time is it
- Almost 9:00 in the morning    - What time does our train arrive
11:00
You know what I'm gonna have for breakfast
What, lemon pie
I'm gonna order a big plate of blueberry pancakes with maple syrup
eggs over easy, and five sausages
Anything to drink with that
Ah, that looks nice
To drink a tall glass of orange juice and a black cup of coffee
After that, I'm going to have a slice of pie
Pie for breakfast
Any time of the day is a good time for pie
Blueberry pie to go with the pancakes
And on top, a thin slice of melted cheese
Where's my watch
It's there
No, it's not
Have you looked
Yes, I fucking looked  What the fuck do you think I'm doing
You sure you got it
Yes  Bedside table drawer
On the little kangaroo
Yes  It was on the little kangaroo
Yeah, well, it's not here now
Well, it should be
It most definitely should be, but it's not here now  So where the fuck is it
Fabienne that was my father's fucking watch
Do you have any idea what he had to go through to get me that watch
I don't have time to go into it, but he went through a lot
All this other shit you could set on fire
but I specifically reminded you not to forget the fucking watch!
Now think  Did you get it
I believe so
You believe so? What the fuck does that mean? You either did, or you didn't get it!
Then I did
Are you sure
No
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Motherfucker!
Do you know how fucking stupid you fucking are
No!
It's not your fault
If you left it at the apartment
If you left it at the apartment, it's not your fault
I had you bring a bunch of stuff
I reminded you about it
but I didn't illustrate how personal the watch was to me
If all I gave a fuck about was the watch I should've told you that
You're not a mind reader, are you
I'm sorry
Don't be  It just means I can't have breakfast with you
Why does it mean that
Because I got to go back to my apartment and get my watch
Won't the gangsters be looking for you there
Well that's what I'm going to find out
If they are and I don't think I can handle it Then I'll split
I saw your watch  I thought I brought it  I'm so sorry
Here's some money  Go out and get those pancakes  Have a nice breakfast  I'll take your Honda
I'll be back before you can say blueberry pie
Blueberry pie
Maybe not that fast but pretty fast, OK
OK
Shit! Of all the fucking things she could fucking forget she forgets my father's watch!
I specifically reminded her  Bedside table, on the kangaroo
I said the words, Don't forget my father's watch
Looking good, Butch
That's how you're going to beat 'em, Butch  They keep underestimating you
Counting flowers on the wall  That don't bother me at all
Playing Solitaire till dawn With a deck of 51
Smoking cigarettes And watching Captain Kangaroo Now, don't tell me
Motherfucker
He's dead
If you need someone to go to court, I'll be glad to help  That guy was a drunken maniac
He hit you, and then he crashed into that car
Who
Him
I'll be damned
Can I help you with something
Shut the fuck up
Now, you just wait a goddamn minute now  What the fuck are you up to
Come here, motherfucker!
You feel that sting, big boy, huh? That's pride fucking with you, see
You got to fight through that shit
You better kill me
Yeah, somebody's going to get killed  Somebody's going to get their motherfucking head blown to
Hold it right there, God damn it
This ain't none of your business, mister
I'm making it my business  Toss the weapon
You don't understand, man
Toss the weapon
Take your foot off the nigger  Put your hands behind your head  Approach the counter right now
This motherfucker's trying to kill me
Shut up  Keep a-coming  Come on
Nobody kills anybody in my place of business except me or Zed
That's Zed
I thought you said you waited for me
I did
So how come they're all beat up
They did that to each other, man  They came in fighting
Now, this one right here, he was going to shoot that one
Is that right? You going to shoot him, boy
Hey, is Grace all right out front
Yeah  It ain't Tuesday, is it
No  It's Thursday
She ought to be fine
Bring out The Gimp
I think The Gimp's sleeping
I guess you'll just have to go wake him up, now, won't you
Get up
Get down
Which one of 'em you want to do first
I ain't for sure yet
Catch a nigger by the toe
If he hollers let him go
My mother said  To pick the perfect one and you are
I guess that means you, big boy
You want to do it in here
No  Let's do it back there in Russell's old room
Sounds good to me
You keep an eye on this one
Shut the fuck up!
You want that gun, don't you, Zed
Go ahead and pick it up
Go ahead, pick it up  Come on  Atta boy
I want you to pick it up Zed
Step aside, Butch
Fuck!
You OK
No, man  I'm pretty fucking far from OK
What now
What now? Let me tell you what now
I'm going to call a couple of hard pipe-hitting niggers to
go to work on the homes here with a pair of pliers and a blow torch
You hear me talking, hillbilly boy
I ain't through with you by a damn sight  I'm going to get medieval on your ass
I meant, what now between me and you
Oh, that what now
I tell you what now between me and you
There is no me and you not no more
So are we cool
Yeah, we cool  Two things
Don't tell nobody about this
This shit is between me, you
and Mr  Soon To Be Living The Rest Of His Short-Ass Life In Agonizing Pain rapist here
It ain't nobody else's business
Two You leave town tonight right now
And when you're gone you stay gone    or you be gone
You lost all your L A  Privileges Deal
Deal
Get your ass out of here
Fabienne!
Fabienne  Come on, baby, come on  Get your shit  We got to go right now
I was so worried  What about our bags
Fuck the bags  If we don't split right now we'll miss the train
I'll be downstairs
Is everything well
Just come on! No talking now
Are we in danger
Come on, honey!
Where did you get this motorcycle
It's not a motorcycle, baby  It's a chopper
What happened to my Honda
I'm sorry, baby  I had to crash that Honda  Will you come on now, please
Come on, let's go, let's go
You're hurt
No, no  I might've broken my nose  It's no biggie  Come on, hop on
Baby, please  Honey, we got to hit the fucking road  Get on
I'm sorry  Come here, come here  I'm sorry  I'm so sorry
You were gone so long I started to think dreadful thoughts
Oh, I'm sorry, sweetie  I didn't mean to worry you
- How was your breakfast?    - It was good
Did you get the blueberry pancakes
They didn't have blueberry pancakes  I had to get buttermilk  Are you sure you're OK
Honey, since I left you, this has been without a doubt the single weirdest fucking day of my life  Come on, hop on  I'll tell you all about it
Come on, get on  Gotta go
Whose motorcycle is this
It's a chopper, baby
Whose chopper is this
- Zed's    - Whose chopper is this?
Zed's dead, baby Zed's dead
(邦妮的状况)
Yes, you did, Brett! You tried to fuck him
And Marsellus Wallace don't like to be fucked By anybody except Mrs  Wallace
Oh, God, please  I don't want to die
- You read the Bible, Brett?  - Yes
Well, there's this passage I got memorized  It sort of fits the occasion
Ezekiel 25:17
The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the selfish and the tyranny of evil men
Blessed is he who in the name of charity and good will
shepherds the weak through the Valley of Darkness
for he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children
And I will strike down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger
those who attempt to poison and destroy My brothers
And you will know My name is the Lord when I lay My vengeance upon thee
I'm fucked  I'm fucked
Is he a friend of yours
Oh, Vincent, Marvin  Marvin, Vincent
Better tell him to shut the fuck up  He's getting on my nerves
Marvin  Marvin! I'd knock that shit off if I was you
Die, you motherfuckers! Die!
Why the fuck didn't you tell us somebody was in the bathroom
You forget someone was in there with a goddamn hand-cannon
You see the size of that gun he fired at us? It was bigger than him
We should be fucking dead, man
I know  We was lucky
No, no, no, no  That shit wasn't luck
Yeah, maybe
This was divine intervention  You know what divine intervention is
I think so
That means that God came down from Heaven and stopped the bullets
That's right  That's exactly what it means  God came down from Heaven and stopped these motherfucking bullets
I think it's time for us to leave, Jules
Don't do that  Don't fucking blow this shit off
What just happened here was a fucking miracle
Chill, Jules  This shit happens
Wrong  Wrong  This shit doesn't just happen
Do you want to continue this theological discussion
in a car or in a jailhouse with the cops
We should be fucking dead, my friend
What happened here was a miracle and I want you to fucking acknowledge it
All right, it was a miracle  Can we go now
Let's go, nigger  Come on
You ever seen that show Cops
I was watching it one time, and there was this cop on and he was talking about this gunfight he had in a hallway with this guy, right?
And he just unloaded on this guy and nothing happened  He didn't hit nothing
OK? It was just him and this guy
I mean, you know it's freaky, but it happens
You want to play blind man, go walk with the shepherd but me, my eyes are wide fucking open
What the fuck does that mean
It means that's it for me  From here on in, you can consider my ass retired
- Jesus Christ  - Don't blaspheme
- God damn it   - I said don't do that
Why are you fucking freaking out on us
Look, I'm telling Marsellus today  I'm through
Why don't you tell him at the same time why
Don't worry  I will
Yeah, and I'll bet you $ 10,000 he laughs his ass off
I don't give a damn if he does
Marvin, what do you make of all this
Man, I don't even have an opinion
You got to have an opinion  Do you think that God came down from Heaven and stopped
What the fuck's happening? Oh, shit, man!
Oh, man, I shot Marvin in the face
Why the fuck did you do that
Well, I didn't mean to do it  It was an accident
Oh, man, I've seen some crazy-ass shit in my time
Chill out, man  I told you it was an accident  You probably    You went over a bump or something
Hey, the car didn't hit no motherfucking bump
Hey, look, man, I didn't mean to shoot the son of a bitch  The gun went off  I don't know why
Well, look at this fucking mess, man! We're on a city street in broad daylight
- I can't believe it, man   - Well, believe it now, motherfucker
We got to get this car off the road
You know, cops tend to notice shit like you're driving a car drenched in fucking blood
Just take it to a friendly place, that's all
This is the Valley, Vincent  Marsellus ain't got no friendly places
Jules, this ain't my fucking town, man!
Shit!
What you doing? I'm calling my partner in Toluca Lake
Where's Toluca Lake? It's just over the hill here, over by Burbank Studios
It's just over the hill here, over by Burbank Studios
If Jimmie's ass ain't home I don't know what the fuck we going to do, man cause I ain't got no other partners in 818
Jimmie, yo, how you doing, man? It's Jules  Just listen up, man
Me and my homeboy are in some serious fucking shit, man  We're in a car, and we got to get off the road pronto
I need to use your garage for a couple hours
We got to be real fucking delicate with this Jimmie situation  He's one remark away from kicking our asses out the door
If he does, what do we do
We ain't leaving till we made a couple calls but I don't want it to reach that pitch
Jimmie's a friend  You don't come into your friend's house and start telling him what's what
Just tell him not to be abusive, that's all
He kind of freaked out back there when he saw Marvin
Well, put yourself in his position  It's 8:00 in the morning  He just woke up  He wasn't expecting this shit
Shit, we got to remember here who's doing who a favor
If that favor means that I got to take shit then he can stick that favor straight up his ass
Nigger, what the fuck did you just do to his towel
I was drying my hands
You're supposed to wash them first
You watched me wash them
I watched you get them wet
I was washing them  This shit's hard to get off
Maybe if he had Lava, I could've done a better job
I used the same fucking soap you did and the towel didn't look like no goddamn maxipad
What if he was to come in here and see his towel like this
It's shit like this that'll bring this situation to a head, man
I ain't threatening you with nothing, all right? You know I respect you and all
but just don't put me in this position, all right
All right  Fine  Fine  Ask me nice like that, no problem
Just go handle your friend  Go ahead  I don't care
Mmm  Goddamn, Jimmie  This is some serious gourmet shit
Me and Vincent would've been satisfied with some freeze-dried Taster's Choice, right
Heh! And he springs this serious gourmet shit on us
What flavor is this? Knock it off, Julie
What
I don't need you to tell me how fucking good my coffee is
I'm the one who buys it  I know how good it is
When Bonnie goes shopping, she buys shit
I buy the gourmet expensive stuff because when I drink it, I want to taste it
But you know what's on my mind right now? It ain't the coffee in my kitchen
It's the dead nigger in my garage
Oh, Jimmie, don't even worry about it
I don't think about anything  I want to ask you a question
When you came pulling in here did you notice a sign out in the front of my house that said Dead Nigger Storage
Jimmie, you know I didn't see no shit
Did you notice a sign in the front of my house that said Dead Nigger Storage
No  I didn't
You know why you didn't see that sign? Why
Cause it ain't there cause storing dead niggers ain't my fucking business!
Jimmie, we're not going to store the motherfucker
Don't you fucking realize, man, that if Bonnie comes home
and finds a body in her house, I'm going to get divorced
No marriage counselor, no trial separation  I'm going to get fucking divorced, OK
And I don't want to get fucking divorced
Now, man, you know, fuck, I want to help you but I don't want to lose my wife doing it, all right
Jimmie, she ain't going to leave you
Don't fucking Jimmie me, Jules! OK? Don't fucking Jimmie me
There's nothing you're gonna say that's gonna make me forget that I love my wife, is there
Look, you know she comes home from work in about an hour and a half
Graveyard shift at the hospital  You got to make some phone calls
You got to call some people? Well, then do it, and get the fuck out of my house before she gets here
That's Kool and the Gang  We don't want to fuck your shit up
I want to call my people, get them to bring us in
You're fucking my shit up right now!
You'll fuck my shit up big time if Bonnie comes home
So just do me that favor, all right? The phone is in my bedroom  I suggest you get going
Well, say she comes home  What do you think she'll do
Oh, no fucking shit, she'll freak  That ain't no kind of answer
I mean, you know, I don't  How much? A lot or a little
You got to appreciate what an explosive element this Bonnie situation is
I mean, if she comes home from a hard day's work
and finds a bunch of gangsters in her kitchen doing a bunch of gangster shit
there ain't no telling what she's liable to do
Yeah, I've grasped that, Jules  All I'm doing is contemplating the ifs
I don't want to hear about no motherfucking ifs
All I want to hear from your ass is You ain't got no problem  I'm on the motherfucker
Go back in there, chill them niggers out and wait for the cavalry, which will be coming directly
You ain't got no problem, Jules  I'm on the motherfucker
Go back in there and chill them niggers out and wait for The Wolf, who should be coming directly
You're sending The Wolf
Oh, you feel better, motherfucker
Shit, negro, that's all you had to say
Is she the hysterical type? When is she due
Give me the principals' names again
Jules  Mm-hmm  Vincent
Jimmie  Bonnie  Mm-hmm
(一具无头尸体)
It's thirty minutes away  I'll be there in ten
(九分二十七秒后)
You're Jimmie, right? This is your house
Sure is
I'm Winston Wolf  I solve problems
Good  We got one
So I heard  May I come in
Yeah, please do
You must be Jules which would make you Vincent
Let's get down to brass tacks, gentlemen  If I was informed correctly the clock is ticking, is that right, Jimmie
100%
Your wife Bonnie comes home at 9:30 in the a m , is that correct
Uh-huh
I was led to believe if she comes home and finds us here she wouldn't appreciate it none too much
She wouldn't at that
That gives us forty minutes to get the fuck out of Dodge
which, if you do what I say when I say it, should be plenty
Now, you got a corpse in a car minus a head in a garage  Take me to it
Jimmie
I thought I smelled some coffee back there  Would you make me a cup
Yeah, sure
Oh, how do you take it
Lots of cream, lots of sugar
About the car is there anything I need to know? Does it stall, smoke, make a lot of noise? Is there gas in it? Anything
Aside from how it looks, the car is cool
Positive? Don't get me out there on the road I find out the brake lights don't work
Man, far as I know, the motherfucker's tiptop
Good enough  Let's go back to the kitchen
Here you go, Mr. Wolf
Thank you, Jimmie
OK, first thing you two, take the body, stick it in the trunk
Now, Jimmie, this looks to be a pretty domesticated house  That would lead me to believe that in the garage or under the sink, you got a bunch of cleaners and shit
Yeah, Mr  Wolf  Under the sink
Good  What I need you two fellas to do is take those cleaning products and clean the inside of the car
I'm talking fast, fast, fast
Go in the back seat scoop up all those little pieces of brain and skull
Get it out of there  Wipe down the upholstery  Now, it don't need to be spick-and-span
You don't need to eat off it  Just give it a good once over
What you need to take care of are the really messy parts
The pools of blood that have collected you got to soak that shit up
Now, Jimmie, we need to raid your linen closet  I need blankets  I need comforters  I need quilts  I need bedspreads
The thicker the better, the darker the better  No whites  Can't use 'em
We need to camouflage the interior of the car
We're going to line the front seat and back seat and the floorboards with quilts and blankets
So if a cop stops us and sticks his big snout in the car the subterfuge won't last
but at a glance, the car will appear to be normal
Jimmie, lead the way  Boys, get to work
Please would be nice
Come again
I said a please would be nice
Get it straight, buster  I'm not here to say please
I'm here to tell you what to do
And if self-preservation is an instinct you possess you better fucking do it and do it quick
I'm here to help  If my help is not appreciated, lots of luck, gentlemen
No, Mr  Wolf, it ain't like that  Your help is definitely appreciated
I don't mean disrespect, OK? I respect you
I don't like people barking orders at me, that's all
If I'm curt with you, it's because time is a factor
I think fast, I talk fast and I need you guys to act fast if you want out of this
so pretty please with sugar on top clean the fucking car
Don't be looking at me like that, all right? I can feel your look
It's a 1974 Chevy Nova  Green
Nothing except for the mess inside
Mmm, about twenty minutes  Nobody who'll be missed
You're a good man, Joe  Thanks a bunch
How we coming, Jimmie
Pretty good  I got it all here but, uh
Mr  Wolf, you got to understand something
Winston, Jimmie, please  Winston
You got to understand something now, Winston
Uh, no, thank you
This is our best linen here
and it was a wedding present from my Uncle Conrad and my Aunt Ginny
and they're not with us anymore  I really want to help you guys out
Let me ask you a question, Jimmie if you don't mind
No, please, go ahead
Your Uncle Conrad and Aunt Ginny were they millionaires
No
Well, your Uncle Marsellus is
and I'm positive if Uncle Conrad and Aunt
Ginny
Ginny were here  they would furnish you with a whole bedroom set
which your Uncle Marsellus is more than happy to do
I like oak myself  That's what I have in my bedroom
How about you, Jimmie? You an oak man
Oak's nice
I will never forgive your ass for this shit  This is some fucked-up repugnant shit
Jules, did you ever hear the philosophy that once a man admits that he is wrong that he is immediately forgiven for all wrongdoings
Get the fuck out my face with that shit  The motherfucker said that shit never had to pick up itty-bitty pieces of skull on account of your dumb ass
I got a threshold, Jules  I got a threshold for the abuse that I will take
Right now, I'm a fucking race car, all right? And you got me in the red  I'm just saying that it's fucking dangerous to have a race car in the fucking red, that's all
- I could blow   - Oh, you ready to blow
Yeah, I'm ready to blow
I'm a mushroom cloud-laying motherfucker, motherfucker
Every time my fingers touch brain, I'm Superfly TNT  I'm The Guns of the Navarone
In fact, what the fuck am I doing in the back
You the motherfucker who should be on brain detail
We fucking switching  I'm washing the windows and you picking up this nigger's skull
Fine job, gentlemen  We may get out of this yet
I can't believe this is the same car
Let's not start sucking each other's dicks quite yet
Phase one is complete    clean the car which moves us right along to phase two clean you two
Strip
All the way
To your bare ass
Quickly, gentlemen
We got about fifteen minutes before Jimmie's better half pulls into the driveway
Damn  This morning air is some chilly shit
Are you sure this is absolutely necessary
- You know what you two look like?   - What
Like a couple of guys who just blew off somebody's head
Stripping off those bloody rags is absolutely necessary
Toss them in Jim's garbage bag
Don't do nothing stupid like leaving this shit out front for Otto the Garbageman you know what I'm saying
Don't worry  We're taking it with us  Jim, the soap
Vincent
OK, gentlemen you've both been to County before I'm sure  Here it comes
Goddamn! The water's fucking cold
Better you than me, gentlemen
Don't be afraid of the soap  Spread it around
Get him up there a little bit
Vincent's hair  Come on, do it, God damn it! Do it!
Towel 'em
They're dry enough  Toss them their clothes
Perfect  We couldn't have planned this better
You guys look like What do they look like, Jimmie
Dorks  They look like a couple of dorks
Ha ha ha  They're your clothes, motherfucker
Come on, gentlemen  We're laughing our way right into prison  Don't make me beg
OK, gentlemen, let's get our rules of the road straight
We're going to a place called Monster Joe's Truck and Tow
Now, Monster Joe and his daughter Raquel are sympathetic to our dilemma
The place is North Hollywood so a few twists and turns aside, we'll be going up Hollywood Way
Now, I'll drive the tainted car  Jules, you ride with me
Vincent, you follow in my Acura
Now, if we come across the path of any John Q  Laws nobody does a fucking thing till I do something
What did I say
- Don't do shit unles   - Unless what
Unless you do it first
Spoken like a true prodigy
How about you, Lash LaRue? Can you keep your spurs from jingling and jangling
Mr  Wolf, look, the gun went off  I don't why  I'm cool  I promise you
Fair enough  Now, I drive real fucking fast, so keep up
If I get my car back any different than I gave it Monster Joe's going to be disposing of two bodies
Out of my way, Rex
We cool
Like it never happened
Boys, this is Raquel
Someday, all this will be hers
You guys going to a volleyball game or something
I'm taking my lady out for breakfast  Maybe I could drop you two off  Where do you live
Redondo
It's    it's your future  L    I see a    a cab ride  Move out of the sticks, fellas
Say good night, Raquel
Good night, Raquel
I'll see you guys around  Stay out of trouble, you crazy kids
Mr  Wolf, I just want to tell you it was a real pleasure watching you work
Yeah, really, and thank you very much, Mr  Wolf
Call me Winston
You see that, young lady? Respect  Respect for one's elders shows character
I have character
Because you are a character doesn't mean that you have character
Want to share a cab
I could go for some breakfast  Feel like having breakfast with me
Cool
I don't know why, I thought he'd be European
Yo, man, he's about as European as English Bob
I know that now, but
Was he cool or what
Totally fucking cool, in control
Didn't even really get pissed when you were fucking with him  I was amazed
Want some bacon
No, man  I don't eat pork
Are you Jewish
Naw, I ain't Jewish  I just don't dig on swine, that's all
Why not
Pigs are filthy animals  I don't eat filthy animals
Yeah, but bacon tastes good  Pork chops taste good
Hey, a sewer rat may taste like pumpkin pie but I'd never know cause I wouldn't eat the filthy motherfuckers
Pigs sleep and root in shit  That's a filthy animal
I ain't eating nothing that ain't got sense enough to disregard its own feces
How about a dog? A dog eats his own feces
I don't eat dog, either
But do you consider a dog to be a filthy animal
I wouldn't go so far as to call a dog filthy but they're definitely dirty
But a dog's got personality  Personality goes a long way
Ah, so by that rationale if a pig had a better personality he would cease to be a filthy animal  Is that true
We'd have to be talking about one charming motherfucking pig
He'd have to be ten times more charming than Arnold on Green Acres, you know what I'm saying
Oh, man, that's good
That's good, man  You're starting to lighten up
You been sitting there all serious and shit
Man, I've just been sitting here thinking
About what
About the miracle we witnessed
The miracle you witnessed  I witnessed a freak occurrence
What is a miracle, Vincent
An act of God
And what's an act of God
God makes the impossible possible
But this morning I don't think qualifies
Don't you see? That shit don't matter  You're judging this shit the wrong way
I mean, it could be God stopped the bullets or he changed Coke to Pepsi, he found my fucking car keys
You don't judge shit like this based on merit
Now, whether or not what we experienced was an According to Hoyle miracle is insignificant
but what is significant is I felt the touch of God  God got involved
But why
Well, that's what's fucking with me  I don't know why, but I can't go back to sleep
You're really thinking about quitting
- The life? - Yeah
Most definitely
What you going to do, then
Well, that's what I've been sitting here contemplating
First, I'm going to deliver this case to Marsellus
Then, basically, I'm just going to walk the earth
What you mean, walk the earth
You know, like Caine in Kung Fu Walk from place to place, meet people, get in adventures
And how long do you intend to walk the earth
Till God puts me where he wants me to be
And what if he don't do that
If it takes forever, then I'll walk forever
So you decided to be a bum
I'll just be Jules, Vincent    no more, no less
No, Jules  You decided to be a bum
Just like all those pieces of shit out there
who beg for change who sleep in garbage bins, eat what I throw away
They got a name for that, Jules  It's called a bum
And without a job, a residence, or legal tender that's what you're going to be, man  You're going to be a fucking bum
Look, my friend, this is just where you and I differ
Garcon! Coffee!
What happened this morning, man, I agree it was peculiar
Garcon means boy  But water into wine  I
All shapes and sizes, Vincent
Don't fucking talk to me that way, man
If my answers frighten you, Vincent then you should cease asking scary questions
I'm going to take a shit
When did you make this decision? When you were sitting there eating that muffin
Well, yeah  I was sitting here eating my muffin and drinking my coffee and replaying the incident in my head
when I had what alcoholics refer to as a moment of clarity
Fuck  To be continued
I love you, Pumpkin
And I love you, Honey Bunny
Everybody be cool! This is a robbery!
Any of you fucking pricks move and I'll execute every one of you motherfuckers!
You got that? You just be quiet! Get the fuck down! Get the fuck down!
You, you're in a blind spot  Take your dames to that booth on the count of ten
Take your dames to that booth on the count of ten  Mexicans out of the fucking kitchen! One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
Hey, you, throw those bags! Fucking wanker! Move! Move!
Grandpa, down!
You're going to give me a problem? No, sir, I'm not  I thought you said you're going to give me a fucking problem! You're going to give me a fucking problem
I think we got a hero here, Honey Bunny!
Well, just execute him!
I am not a hero  I'm just a coffee shop
The restaurant's ours!
Just take whatever you want
- You talk to the customers   - Yeah
You tell them to be fucking cool and everything will be over! You understand me
Yes
Listen, everybody  Be calm cooperate and this will all be over in a minute
Get the fuck down! Well done
All right, now, people I'm going to come around and collect your wallets
You don't fucking talk  You just throw them in the bag  Are we clear? I said, are we fucking clear
Good  Now wallets out
That's it  Get the fuck down  In the bag  In the fucking bag!
I don't have nothing on me, man
What am I waiting for? In the fucking bag
Laura? Laura, tips  In the bag  Yeah
Is that a cellular phone? Yeah  In the fucking bag
Tidy up, tidy up  That's it  Now get the fuck down on the floor
In the bag
What's in the case
My boss's dirty laundry
Your boss makes you do his laundry
When he wants it clean
Sounds like a shit job
Funny  I was thinking the same thing
Open it
Afraid I can't do that
I didn't hear you
Yes, you did
What's going on
Looks like we got a vigilante in our midst
Shoot him in the face
I hate to shatter your ego, but this ain't the first time I've had a gun pointed at me
You don't take your hand off that case, it'll be your last
Stop causing problems! You'll get us all killed! Give 'em what you got and get 'em out of there!
Shut the fuck up, fat man! This ain't none of your goddamn business
Be cool, Honey Bunny  Be cool
Now I'm going to count to three
If you don't open that case I'm going to unload in your fucking face
We clear
one
three  OK, Ringo  You win
It's yours
Open it
What is it? What is it
Is that what I think it is
Mm-hmm
It's beautiful
God damn it, what is it
You let him go! You let him go! Let go of him!
Tell that bitch to be cool! I'm gonna kill you! Say, Bitch, be cool! Be cool, Honey Bunny!
Say, Bitch, be cool! Be cool!
Tell that fucking bitch to chill!
Be cool, Honey Bunny!
Chill that fucking bitch out!
Chill out, Honey Bunny!
- Let go of him! - JULES: Chill!
Promise her!
I promise!
Tell her to chill!
Just chill out, Honey Bunny!
- Now tell me her name   - Yolanda
All right, now, Yolanda!  We're not gonna do anything stupid, are we
Don't you hurt him!
Nobody's gonna hurt anybody  We're all gonna be like three little Fonzies here  And what's Fonzie like
Come on, Yolanda, what's Fonzie like?
- He's cool?   - What
- Cool    - Correctamundo
And that's what we're gonna be  We're gonna be cool
Now, Ringo, I'm gonna count to three  And when I count three
I want you to let go of your gun put your palms flat on the table and sit your ass down
But when you do it, you do it cool  You ready
One  two  three
OK, now you let him go!
Yolanda, I thought you were gonna be cool  Now, when you yell at me, it makes me nervous
And when I get nervous, I get scared  And when motherfuckers get scared that's when motherfuckers accidentally get shot
Just know, you hurt him, you die  Well, that seems to be the situation
But I don't want that, and you don't want that and Ringo here definitely doesn't want that
So let's see what we can do
here's the situation
Normally both your asses would be dead as fucking fried chicken
but you happened to pull this shit while I'm in a transitional period
and I don't want to kill you  I want to help you
But I can't give you this case, 'cause it don't belong to me
Besides, I been through too much shit over this case to just hand it over to your dumb ass
Vincent! Be cool!
Yolanda, it's cool, baby! It's cool!
We still just talking! Come on, point the gun at me! Point the gun at me! There you go
Now, Vincent, you just hang back and don't do a goddamn thing  Tell her we're still cool
We're still cool, Honey Bunny
How we doing, baby
I gotta go pee  I want to go home
Just hang in there, baby  You're doin' great  I'm proud of you
And Ringo's proud of you  It's almost over
Tell her you're proud of her
I'm proud of you, Honey Bunny
I love you
I love you, too, Honey Bunny
I want you to go in that bag and find my wallet
Which one is it
It's the one that says Bad Motherfucker
That's my Bad Motherfucker
Open it up  Take out the money
Count it
How much is there
About $1,500
OK, put it in your pocket  It's yours
With the rest of those wallets and the register that makes this a pretty successful little score
Jules, you give that fucking nimrod $ 1,500 and I'll shoot him on general principle
No, Yolanda, Yolanda! He ain't gonna do a goddamn mother fucking thing Vince, shut the fuck up!
Come on, Yolanda, stay with me, baby  Now, I ain't giving it to him, Vincent
I'm buying something for my money
Wanna know what I'm buying, Ringo
What
Your life  I'm giving you that money so I don't have to kill your ass
You read the Bible, Ringo
Not regularly, no
Well, there's this passage I got memorized
Ezekiel 25:17
The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the selfish and the tyranny of evil men
Blessed is he who in the name of charity and good will
shepherds the weak through the Valley of Darkness
for he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children
And I will strike down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger
those who attempt to poison and destroy My brothers
And you will know I am the Lord when I lay My vengeance upon you
Now, I been saying that shit for years  And if you heard it, that meant your ass
I never gave much thought to what it meant  I just thought it was some cold-blooded shit to say to a motherfucker before I popped a cap in his ass
But I saw some shit this morning made me think twice
See, now I'm thinking maybe it means you're the evil man and I'm the righteous man
and Mr  Nine-millimeter here he's the shepherd protecting my righteous ass in the Valley of Darkness
Or it could mean you're the righteous man and I'm the shepherd
and it's the world that's evil and selfish
Now, I'd like that  But that shit ain't the truth
The truth is you're the weak and I am the tyranny of evil men
But I'm trying, Ringo  I'm trying real hard to be the shepherd
Go on
I think we should be leaving now
Yeah, that's probably a good idea
剧终·谢谢观赏